Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer
And Prophecy In Jesus' Name
Can I talk to you?
How are you?
Pray against depression.
Yes.
- Are you with me?
- Yes.
Depression is in the family.
Yes.
This is suicide in the family - it's a suicide problem.
But the Lord loves you. Okay?
Okay, thank you.
For you to come before Christ - Jesus loves you.
Thank you.
You are depressed and many things are going on in your heart.
Okay.
This is from your father's side.
- From my father's side?
- Yes.
Because my father always tells me that I'm crazy.
My father is actually a minister, like a pastor, but he is retired.
He doesn't believe in hell, so he lives in sin.
It's really difficult.
So, don't worry. Jesus loves you.
Thank you.
This is a blessing of God for you today, to tell you that there is a challenge, a court case.
Thank You, Lord.
Come on! Stand up!
Come here!
In the name of Jesus!
Come on! Bring her out!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer
And Prophecy In Jesus' Name
In the name of Jesus, out!
Leave her!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer
And Prophecy In Jesus' Name
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer
And Prophecy In Jesus' Name
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Who are you?
Come here! Come this direction!
In the name of Jesus!
Come here!
Who are you?
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
TESTIMONY TIME
My name is Heide Menzel. I come from Germany.
T.B. Joshua told me that I have a spirit of depression, a spirit of suicide,
and that there is a controversy about a child from my father's side.
I was very amazed.
This is the answer I had been longing for for a very long time.
When I look back, I can see that it affected my whole life
since I was a small kid, actually since I was born.
I had flashbacks from the time I was a baby.
I felt rejected and stopped crying.
When I grew older, at the age of 6 or 7, I asked God why I'm alive
when nobody likes me anyway, and I tried to kill myself.
But I don't know - by the grace of God, I always believed in Him
and always believed in hell.
The knowledge that Heaven and hell are real saved my life.
So you mean from a very small age, this spirit of suicide entered you
and you heard voices telling you to end your life. Is that right?
Yes.
Can you explain, as you grew up, how these voices tormented you
and how many times that thought of ending your life actually came to you.
Actually, I totally focused on the future. I was not living at the present anymore.
Many times I thought about taking my life.
I had nightmares every night -
nightmares about someone trying to kill me.
This affected my whole life.
My whole life I felt rejected.
I felt that I was imprisoned in myself; I didn't feel comfortable.
I didn't like my body and my character.
My whole life I actually thought something was wrong with me,
and I just didn't know what it was.
The problem was: I tried to get close to Jesus but there was a barrier.
I couldn't reach a certain kind of point.
So I became very religious, I focused on the Old Testament,
I did a lot of fasting like the Easter fasting.
I tried to manipulate Jesus and God whilst I was fasting.
I went so far that I even quit my job - I was a senior plant buyer -
to give everything away. I had a very fancy apartment.
So as to force Jesus to answer me.
I had only my car left, slept inside the car
and said, "Lord, here I am. Now, please answer me"
because I knew there is no other way than Jesus; there is no alternative.
But there was a barrier I couldn't get past.
It was very bad. In my heart I knew I needed deliverance
so I started doing self-deliverance.
I started to search on YouTube and I also found Emmanuel TV.
What happened when you started watching Emmanuel TV on YouTube?
It was actually about a year ago.
I was amazed; I couldn't stop watching it.
All those people I saw there had the same problem I had.
They got somehow stuck; they didn't know where the barrier was.
In fact, I wasn't even aware that I had this spirit of suicide and depression
because I numbed my feelings; I was so used to being like this -
in this kind of unhappy lifestyle - that I didn't even think about it.
Since that time, I had this huge urge inside of me:
I had to come here somehow.
I started to pray along with T.B. Joshua - the prayers for the viewers.
That's when I came here.
So can you tell us - when you finally came here,
and Prophet T.B. Joshua gave you that word of prophecy and you were delivered in Jesus' name,
what did you experience when you received that touch and that prophecy?
It was a miracle for me because before, I was at a stage
where just like Luke 16, Lazarus, I said, "God, I don't know what to do anymore.
I just endure; I want to overcome.
I need help; I don't understand what is going on.
I can't get out of it myself.
When T.B. Joshua told me this prophecy, it was a big relief.
A lot of prayers got answered.
I was so thankful - I am so thankful.
Thank you.
So after the prophecy and the deliverance, can you tell us -
what are the changes that you have seen in your life and your thoughts?
Actually, before I came here, I was always tired.
Last year, I experienced a very high tension; I couldn't calm down anymore.
I was very anxious and stressed.
Since that deliverance, I have been calm - for the first time in years.
I was addicted to coffee.
I stopped drinking coffee in the morning.
I got up at 2 am for prayers.
The barrier that was between me and Jesus is gone.
Now, I can rebuild a completely new relationship to God.
The things that were hindering me, to come close to God...
I'm so thankful for that; I'm so grateful. Thank you.
Hallelujah! Let's clap for wonderful Jesus Christ!
You mentioned that before: Because of this spirit of suicide,
every night you would experience nightmares or people were trying to kill you in your dreams.
Ever since your deliverance, how have you been sleeping?
It's fine; it's perfect.
I feel calm.
I have a joy I had only very few times in my life when I was at church.
Here, it feels like coming home.
It's spirit-filled. I want to kiss the whole world.
I want to thank everyone; I'm so full of love.
It is just amazing.
I'm so happy; I'm very happy.
Hallelujah! Let's clap for Jesus Christ!
So, madam, after God has delivered you from that spirit of suicide and depression,
and brought that joy back into your life,
millions around the world that are suffering from the same problem want to learn from you.
What would your advice be?
Please endure because Jesus, by His grace, saved me from being dead for a long time
just because I knew there was hell.
Don't end your life because there is someone:
There is Jesus who loves you more than you could ever imagine.
I also love you. Don't do it.
Don't kill yourself because satan hates you and if you kill yourself, you go to hell.
And hell is the worst place you could ever imagine.
I believe your situation is very bad right now.
Very bad - probably worse than mine.
But believe me, if you go to hell, it will be a thousand times worse, and it is not worth it.
If you need help, come to this place and get delivered.
I wasn't even aware that I had that spirit of suicide.
It was a big relief to find out.
It was actually obvious but I didn't think about it.
So please, I'm begging you, make God your protection.
I can tell because I used to be a backpacker.
He protected me at least twice from being raped.
When you have God as your protection, He guides you.
My prayer for you is what I prayed when I was facing hard times:
God, if I ever leave you, please take me by the hand and bring me back.
This is my prayer for you that God holds your hand
and brings you to a place where you can get delivered and find peace.
And you have to know that the spirit of suicide, when you want to kill yourself,
is a spirit which hates you and you can get rid of it.
Please, don't waste your life
and come to a place like this where it is like Heaven on earth.
Please...
Amen.
Heide Menzel
Prophecy Testimony
So we have heard from our sister. That is a wonderful advice,
telling everyone that has that thought of trying to kill oneself
that there is a spirit behind it - a spirit of suicide.
They should be open for deliverance and remember, God loves them.
And we should never doubt God's ability or desire to rescue us from every situation.
Our problem, whatever it may be, does not embarrass Jesus Christ because He has a solution.
We thank God for your life and your deliverance.
We want to encourage you: Now that you have received this wonderful deliverance in Christ,
you should be ruled by the Word of God
so that you continue to maintain this wonderful joy, in Jesus' name.
Thank you, everybody!
TT: Mel Flowers 22/08/2018
RV ROBERT BEGIER 28/08/2018